let's discuss the solution for the
second performance comparison quiz now
the laptop that we had took 10 minutes
and the new one takes 4 hours because we
are actually using the old laptop to do
this the speed up is equal to the
latency of the previous thing which is
10 minutes divided by the latency of the
new thing we're using which is 240 so
this time the speed up is 0.04 so the
correct answer here is 0.04
again if there is an actual slowdown
from the previous thing to the new thing
we're using then we can expect the speed
up to be lower than one and if we got
instead 24 as our answer that should
mean that whatever we are using now is
faster than before so that should tell
us that something is wrong so pretty
much by kind of checking if it makes
sense you know is the new thing actually
having a speed up as opposed to slowdown
if it is a speed up it should be above
one a speed up lower than one is an
actual Slowdown